Faculty Reference; Collection ua950.003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- F, 1851-2005; 6
  - Forget, Gerard, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Forman, Carol, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fornari, Daniel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Forsyth, Elaine, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Forsyth, John, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Fossa, Philip, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fossett, James W., Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Foster, Philip J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fotheringham, David J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fossieck, Theodore Henry, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fossieck, Theodore, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Foti, Patrick A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fox, Charles, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Fox, Cynthia, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Fox, Joseph Michael, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Fox, Paul J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Fox, Paul J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Fox, Paul Jefferey, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Fraley, Ruth A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Fraley, Ruth Ann, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Francis, Carol, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Francis, Patricia, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Franconere, Vincent, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Frangos, George, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Frangos, George D., Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Frank, Francine, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Frank, Joachim, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Franklin, Lee, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Frederick, Robert W., Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Freedman, Michael B., Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Frelick, John P., Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - French, William M., Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Frenkel, Eleanor, Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Frenkel, Gerald D., Undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Freund, Heidi, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Frey, William, Undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Friedlander, Myrna L., Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Friedlander, Walter, Undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Friedman, Nathaniel A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Friedman, Nathaniel A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Friedman, Neil, Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Friedman, Sally, Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Friedman Sally, Undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Friedman, Susan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Frink, Helen H., Undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Frinta, Mojmir, Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Frinta, Mojmir Svatopluk, Undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Frisch, Harry L., 1967-1999 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Fritz, Barbara L., Undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Froebig, Jean, Undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Frost, Robert E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Frye, Cheryl, Undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Fryling, Margaret S., Undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Fukushima, Takashi, Undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Fukushima, Takashi, Undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Funnelle, Amanda Parker, 1864 April-1866 November (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Fuoco, Cadance A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Furst, Peter, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Furst, Peter T., Undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Futia, Agostino, Undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Futterer, Agnes E., 1917-1959 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- G, 1851-2005; 7
  - Gabriel, Brian E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Gabriel, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Gadre, Anand, Undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Gage, Timothy, Undated (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Gager, C. Stuart, Undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Galembo, Phyllis, Undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Gallant, Mary, Undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Gallup, Gordon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Gallup, Gordon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Gallup, Gordon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Gallup, Gordon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Gallup, Gordon, Undated (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Galuski, Kevin, Undated (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Galvin, Thomas J., Undated (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Gambari, Ibrahim A., Undated (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Gambari, Ibrahim, Undated (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Gamble, John, Undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Ganeles, Daniel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Ganeles, Daniel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Garafola, Laurie, Undated (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Garber, Eugene, Undated (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Garber, Eugene, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Garcia, Barbara, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Garcia, Joseph, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Garcia Jose (Joe), Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gardner, Randolf, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gardner, Randolph S., Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Garg, Jagadish, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Harhart, Johnathan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Garg, Jagadish, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Garland, Martha, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Garofalo, James, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Garthwaite, Paul E., Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Garvin, Robert M., Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Garvin, Robert M., Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Gascoyne, Richard Clark, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Gates, Gary W., Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Gatti, Timothy H., 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Gatto, Dan-Barber, 1967-2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Gatto, Daniel, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Gavryck, Jacquelyn A., Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Gavryck, Jacquelyn, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Gaylord, Linda, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Gebhardt, Thomas L., Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Geary, Travis, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Geer, Robert, Undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Gehring, Charles, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Geiger, Jay, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Gelfand, Jack E., Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Gelzheiser, Lynn, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Gemmel, James, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Genshaft, July Lynn, 1992-997 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Geoffrion, Leo D., Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - George, Peter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Georges, Daniel, Undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Gerba, Janet S., Undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Gerber, John, Undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Gerber, Robert I., Undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Germain, Carol Anne, Undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Germain, Carol Anne, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Ghiradella, Helen, Undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Ghiso-Aguirre, Julio, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Giarusso, John, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Gewirtz, Mindy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Giaver, Ivar, Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Gibson, David, Undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Gibson, Jeffery K., Undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Gibson, Kathryn, Undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Gibson, Robert H., Undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Gifford, Roger D., Undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Gilbert, David, Undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Gilbert, Linda, Undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Gilbert, Virginia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Gilchrist, Eugene A., Undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Giles, Freda Scott, Undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Gillis, Carolyn, Undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Gillis, Kendra, Undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Gilliam, James F., Undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Gillispie, Gregory D., Undated (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Gilman, Charlote P., Undated (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Gilman, Irvin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Gilman, Irvin E., Undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, Undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Ginsberg, Warren, Undated (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Ginsberg, Warren, Undated (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Gioia, Vito, Undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Giovane, Frank, Undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Gisdfi, Anthony, 1964 September-1976 June 10 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Glanz, Joseph, Undated (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Gmelch, George J., Undated (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Gjaja, Vesna, Undated (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Glass, Julia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Glover, Douglas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Glover, Douglas, Undated (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Gluck, Robert J., Undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Goatley, Virginia, Undated (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Goel, Sanjay, Undated (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Goggin, Mary, Undated (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Gold, Maxine S., Undated (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Gold, Steven D., Undated (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Golden, Edward, Undated (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Goldfarb, Owen, Undated (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Goldin, Liliana, Undated (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Goldman, Richard, Undated (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Goldman, Richard, Undated (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Goldsberry, Lisa James, Undated (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Goldstein, Ken, Undated (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Goldstein, Phyllis, Undated (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Goldstein, Richard Z., Undated (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Goldstein, Walter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Goldstein, Walter, Undated (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Gonzalez, Henry R., Undated (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Gonzalez, Lisa, Undated (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Goodman, Carl F., Undated (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Goodman, David, Undated (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Goodman, Richard A., Undated (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Goodwin, Danny, Undated (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Gootzeit, Michael J., Undated (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Gordis, Elana, Undated (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Gordon, Gilbert, 1968 February 28 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Gordon, Hugh, Undated (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Gordon, Hugh, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Gordon, Hugh, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Gordon, Hugh, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Gordon, Leonard V., Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Gordon, Leonard Victor, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Gordon, Vivian, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Gossen, Eleanor, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gossen, Eleanor Adam, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gossen, Gary, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Gottfredson, Michael, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Gottschalk, Nathan, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Gould, Josiah B., Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Gould, Samuel B., 1963-1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Grainger, Anthony, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Gouraige, Ghislain, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Gradus, Nora, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Grava, Arnolds, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Grava, Arnolds, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Grava, Arnolds, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Green, Jerry E., Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Green, John, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Green, John Arthur, 1975 February 10 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Green, Matie E., Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Green, Michael, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Green, Suzanne, Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Greenberg, J. Mayo, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Greenberg, J. Mayo, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Greene, Robert, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Greenfeld, Norman, Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Greenfield, Norman, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Greenwold, Mark, Undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Gregg, Lois Hamilton, Undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Gregory, Kim, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Greiman, Jennifer, Undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), 1918-1988 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Griffith, Glynne, Undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Griggs-Janower, David, Undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Griggs-Janower, David, Undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Grignon, Albina, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Grignon, Albina, Undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Grimes, William V., Undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Grimes, William V. Jr., Undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Groark, James J., Undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Groark, James, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Groark, James J., Undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Groat, Douglas F., Undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Gronberg, Dianne I., Undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Gronberg, Dianne I., Undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Grondahl, Paul, Undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Grossberg, Daniel, Undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Grossberg, Millie, Undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Gruenewald, Thomas, Undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Gruner, William J., Undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Grupta, Ravindra, Undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Guarino, Eugene, Undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Guarino, Eugene A., Undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Guarino, Eugene A., Undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Guastello, Richard, Undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Guha, Susanta R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Guha, Susanta R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Guha, Susanta R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Guha, Susanta R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Guha, Susanta R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Guidotti, Don, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Guithart, Jorge, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gullahorn, Jean, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Gullahorn, Jean, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Gullotta, Frank, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gummer, Burton, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Gunn, John Martynn, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Gunnell, John, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Gunnell, John G., Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Gunnell, John G., Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Guney, Senem, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Gurney, Kathleen, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gustina, David, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
- H, 1851-2005; 8
  - Haas, Andrew, Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Haas, Shari, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Haase, Richard F., Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Haber, Judith P., Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Haberer, Robert, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Haberl, Arthur, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Haboush, William J., Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Hagan, Georgette, Undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Hagan, Jan L., Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Haggerty, John P., Undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Hahner, June, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Haile, Christine, Undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Haile, Christine, Undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Haine, Robert, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Haines, John, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Hairston, Creasie F., Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Haldar, Pradeep, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Haldowski, Timothy, Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Hale, Clarence F., Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Hall, Ethel, 1900-2000 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Hall, Kermit, Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Hall, Kermit, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Hall, Kermit, Undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Hall, Kermit, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Hall, Kermit L., 1944-2006 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Hall, Richard, Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Hallenbeck, James, Undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Hallenbeck, James Paul, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Halpern, Leslie Fay, Undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Halter, Helen, Undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Haltzel, Helen N., Undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Hamberg, Marie, Undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Hamdi, Mary Evans, Undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Hamilton, Harry, Undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Hamilton, Harry Lemuel Jr., Undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Hamilton, La Verne, Undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Hamlin, Walter, Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Hamm, Richard, Undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Hammer, Peter, Undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Hammond, William, Undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Hammond, William, Undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Hanani, Yehuda, Undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Hancock, Charles, Undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Hancock, Charles R., Undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Handy, Ernest V., Undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Hanes, Steven, Undated (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Hanft, Richard A., Undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Hanifan, Jil, Undated (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Hanks, Jane, Undated (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Hanley, Jerome, Undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Hannan, Edward, Undated (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Hannay, Margaret, Undated (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Hanner, Martha, Undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Hannigan, John, Undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Hannigan, John H., Undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Hanson, David J., Undated (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Hanson, Pat, Undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Hardiman, Eric, Undated (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Harding, Constance J., Undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Harding, Constance Joy, Undated (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Hardt, Robert H., Undated (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Hardt, Sandy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hardy, William G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hardford, Jon, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Hargett, James, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Hargett, James, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Harmon, Thomas, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Harper, Gregory, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Harper, Gregory, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Harrington, Charles F., Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Harrington, Jack, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Harrington, Susan M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Harris, Ann, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Harris, Joanne, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Rachel S., Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Harrison, Lee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Harrison, Teresa, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Harrison, T. Mark, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Harrison, Timothy M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Hart, Amy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Hart, Rodney A., Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Hartgen, David T., Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Hartigan, John A., Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Hartley, John, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Hartman, Charles, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Hartmark, Leif, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Hartzell, Karl Drew, Jr., Undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Haskins, Motier, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Hastings, George, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Hastings, George, Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Hastings, George, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Hathaway, Eleanor R., Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Hathaway, Eleanor Roth, 1948 January 15 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Haugard, Jeffrey J., Undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Hauser, Frank, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Hauser, Richard S., 1948-1996 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Hauser, Richard S., Undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Hauser, Muriel, Undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Havens, Janet M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Haviland, Morrison, Undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Haviland, Morrison C., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Hawkins, Lester G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Hawkins, Lester G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Hayes, John T., 1984 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Hays, Samuel H., 1970-1988 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Hayward, Horton, Undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Hazard, Brenda, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Head, Brian F., Undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Healey, James J., Undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Heaphey, James, Undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Heaphey, James J., Undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Heaphey, Joan, Undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Hearst, George, Undated (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Hebert, Andy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Hebert, Lloyd, Undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Hechinger, Fred, Undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Hedberg, Bill, Undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Hedge, Krishna G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Hedges, Robert, Undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Hedges, Roman B., Undated (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Heighton, Paula-Christy, Undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Heikoff, Joseph M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Heimberg, Richard, Undated (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Heimberg, Richard G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Heiser, Wayne, Undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Heiser, W. Wayne, Undated (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Heiss, Ann M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Heller, Charles, Undated (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Heller, Frieda, Undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Helmrich, Dennis, Undated (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Helmrich, Dennis, Undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Helsby, Robert D., Undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Hemenway, Curtis L., Undated (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Hemenway, Curtis L., Undated (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Henderson, Floyd, Undated (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Henderson, Floyd M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Henderson, Floyd M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Hendricks, Mike, Undated (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Henighan, John G., 1969-1994 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Hennessy, Rosemary, Undated (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Hennett, Alisha, Undated (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Henrikson, Craig, Undated (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Henrikson, Craig, Undated (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Henrikson, Craig Ernest, Undated (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Henrikson, Craig Ernest, Undated (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Henry, Jon, Undated (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Herbst, Susan, Undated (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Herkowitz, Gloria, Undated (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Herkowitz, Gloria M., Undated (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Herlands, Marty, Undated (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Herlihy, John G., Undated (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Herman, Catherine, Undated (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Herman, Robert S., Undated (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Herman, Robert S., Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Herman, Robert S., Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hernandez, Browdy Jennifer, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hernandez, Donald, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Herriott, Arthur W., Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Herron, Bruce, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Herzel, Roger, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Herzel, Roger W., Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Herzig, Abbe, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Herzog, Bette R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Herzstein, Robert, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Hester, Donald G., Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hester, Richard, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Heter, Frank E., Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Hewat, Nancy C., Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hewitt, Ryland H., Jr., Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Hewitt, Ryland Hugh, Jr., Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Hickox, Edward, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Hicks, Scott, Undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Higginbotham, James T., Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Higgins, A.C., Undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Higgins, Albert C., Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Higgins, Brian, 1988 April 21 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Hildreth, Anne, Undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Hildebrand, Martin Victor, Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Hill, Inez, Undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Hill, Johnetta, Undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Hill, LaMar, Undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Hill, Mike, Undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Hillebrand, Gary R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Hilles, Carolyn R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Hindelang, Michael J., Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Hindley, Clarence B., 1952 June 24 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Hines, Edward R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Hindeling, Michael J., Undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Hirsch, Helmut V.B., Undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Hirsch, Helmut, Undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Hirschenson, Cheryl, Undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Hirschi, Travis, Undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Hirschi, Travis, Undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Hirtle, Shephen C., Undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Hitchcock, Arthur A., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Hitchcock, Arthur, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, Undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, Undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Hitchcock, Karen, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated (Box 18, Folder 59)